{"pokemon": [
	{"question": "Charmeleon evolves into Charizard to fight which pokemon?", "answer": "Aerodactyl"},
	{"question": "Ash Ketchum wins the 'Pokemon Race' with which Pokemon?", "answer": "Rapidash"},
	{"question": "Which is the legendary dog fire Pokemon of Johto?", "answer": "Entei"},
	{"question": "Weezing belongs to who?", "answer": "James"},
	{"question": "What is Gastly's secondary type except ghost?", "answer": "Poison"},
	{"question": "What is the last move Charizard used to defeat Pidgeot?", "answer": "Seismic toss"},
	{"question": "In the episode 'Gymbaliar', what Pokemon does Brock catch?", "answer": "Croagunk"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does James get in the episode 'Two Degrees of Separation'?", "answer": "Carnivine"},
	{"question": "In 'Gettin' Twiggy With it', what Pokemon does Ash catch?", "answer": "Turtwig"},
	{"question": "What is the name of the new girl Ash and Brock meet in the Sinnoh Region?", "answer": "Dawn"},
	{"question": "What type is Lucario?", "answer": "Fighting and Steel"},
	{"question": "I want to be the best Pokemon master ever. Who am I?", "answer": "Ash"},
	{"question": "I was Ash's very first Pokemon. Who am I?", "answer": "Pikachu"},
	{"question": "I am Ash's female traveling companion from the Sinnoh region. I want to be a top Pokemon coordinator. Who am I?", "answer": "Dawn"},
	{"question": "I am Ash's male traveling companion. I am the former gym leader from Pewter City. Who am I?", "answer": "Brock"},
	{"question": "I am Ash's rival from the Sinnoh region. I only care about strong Pokemon and release any Pokemon that is weak or does not reach my standards. Who am I?", "answer": "Paul"},
	{"question": "I am the female member of Team Rocket. I have pinkish-red hair and blue eyes. I am self centered and care about my hair and makeup. Who am I?", "answer": "Jessie"},
	{"question": "I am the male member of Team Rocket. I have purple hair and green eyes. I am evil a lot of the time, but sometimes I show a caring side. Who am I?", "answer": "James"},
	{"question": "I am a Pokemon and a member of Team Rocket. I am one of only a few Pokemon that can talk. Who am I?", "answer": "Meowth"},
	{"question": "I am a fire type Pokemon that resembles a monkey. I was released by Paul because he thought I was weak. After this event, Ash offered for me to join his team. Who am I?", "answer": "Chimchar"},
	{"question": "What are Bagon's two weaknesses?", "answer": "Dragon and Ice"},
	{"question": "When fighting a Xatu, a Spark attack will do more damage than Fire Blast.", "answer": "True"},
	{"question": "Which move will do the most damage to an Altaria?", "answer": "Blizzard"},
	{"question": "How many members are there of the Squirtle Squad?", "answer": "5"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon, in the episode 'Bulbasaur and the Hidden Village', did Misty want to catch?", "answer": "Oddish"},
	{"question": "What was the name of Charmander's original trainer?", "answer": "Damien"},
	{"question": "Who kicked Mankey?", "answer": "James"},
	{"question": "Where is the Tower of Terror located?", "answer": "Lavender Town"},
	{"question": "In the episode 'Bulbasaur and the Hidden Village', what is Bulbasaur's special attack?", "answer": "Vine Whip"},
	{"question": "Which city did Ash reach after capturing Primeape?", "answer": "Celadon City"},
	{"question": "Ash's hat is an official Pokemon League hat.", "answer": "true"},
	{"question": "How many Pokemon lived in the Tower of Terror?", "answer": "3"},
	{"question": "What is May's brother's name?", "answer": "Max"},
	{"question": "Does May's brother have any Pokemon?", "answer": "No"},
	{"question": "What was May's first Pokemon?", "answer": "Torchic"},
	{"question": "What was Brock before he joined Ash on his journey?", "answer": "A gym leader"},
	{"question": "What type of Pokemon does Misty have?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "Does May have a Bulbasaur?", "answer": "yes"},
	{"question": "What is the name of the nurse in all the Pokemon centers?", "answer": "Joy"},
	{"question": "One episode taken out of U.S. rotation because of the events of 9-11.", "answer": "true"},
	{"question": "The episode, 'Electric Soldier Porygon,' give 700 Japanese children seizures.", "answer": "true"},
	{"question": "Another episode, 'Holiday at Acapulco,' caused problems because of ...", "answer": "A cross-dressing man"},
	{"question": "How many episodes were delayed because they were 'too Japanese'?", "answer": "2"},
	{"question": "In the episode 'Princess vs. Princess,' which Pokemon did Misty win the competition with?", "answer": "Psyduck"},
	{"question": "In 'The Purr-fect Hero,' what Japanese holiday was being celebrated?", "answer": "Kids' Day"},
	{"question": "Most of the problem episodes appeared during which season?", "answer": "First"},
	{"question": "What year were the Christmas specials aired in the U.S.?", "answer": "1999"},
	{"question": "'Slowking's Day' appears in what season?", "answer": "3"},
	{"question": "Brock has how many brothers and sisters?", "answer": "9"},
	{"question": "How many years had the Maiden of Maiden's Peak waited for her true love to return to her?", "answer": "2,000 years"},
	{"question": "What is the name of the trainer who was waiting for Ash in the Viridian Forest?", "answer": "Samurai"},
	{"question": "Who gave Ash his first Pokemon?", "answer": "Professor Oak"},
	{"question": "In which city did Ash's first gym battle take place?", "answer": "Pewter City"},
	{"question": "What is the name of the famous stone that was believed to come from outer space?", "answer": "Moon Stone"},
	{"question": "What is Brock's father's name?", "answer": "Flint"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does James buy aboard the St. Anne?", "answer": "Magikarp"},
	{"question": "James comes from a rich family.", "answer": "True"},
	{"question": "What is the only move Ditto can learn?", "answer": "Transform"},
	{"question": "Which Pokemon steals other pokemon for his trainer?", "answer": "Farfetch'd"},
	{"question": "What attack does Gyarados use to get Ash, Misty, Brock, Pikachu, and Team Rocket away?", "answer": "Dragon Rage"},
	{"question": "Whose bike does Ash break?", "answer": "Misty"},
	{"question": "Which Pokemon's song puts everyone to sleep?", "answer": "Jigglypuff"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon hatched from Ash's egg?", "answer": "Phanpy"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon did Misty catch in the Whirl Islands?", "answer": "Corsola"},
	{"question": "What two Pokemon save Ash's egg from being stolen by Team Rocket?", "answer": "Togepi and Kangaskhan"},
	{"question": "What color was Ash's egg?", "answer": "blue"},
	{"question": "What did Sakura's Eevee evolve into?", "answer": "Espeon"},
	{"question": "Did Ash leave Bulbasaur with Prof. Oak in 'Bulbasaur... The Ambassador'?", "answer": "yes"},
	{"question": "Who pretended he was Prof. Oak in 'Will The Real Oak Please Stand Up'?", "answer": "James"},
	{"question": "What was the name of the baby Lugia?", "answer": "Silver"},
	{"question": "What is the name of the guy who wanted to catch Suicune?", "answer": "Eusine"},
	{"question": "What is the name of Richie's Pikachu?", "answer": "Sparky"},
	{"question": "Is Professor Oak Gary's grandpa?", "answer": "True"},
	{"question": "Lugia is intended to be the guardian of what?", "answer": "Legendary Bird Pokemon"},
	{"question": "Which Pokémon was gifted to Misty by Tracey?", "answer": "Azurill"},
	{"question": "There are how many variations of Unown?", "answer": "28"},
	{"question": "Who created Mewtwo?", "answer": "Giovanni"},
	{"question": "What was the first Pokemon to appear in the animated series?", "answer": "Gengar"},
	{"question": "Which Pokemon's Pokedex reference number is the same as the first three digits of its weight in pounds?", "answer": "Scyther"},
	{"question": "Gyarados was modeled after what legendary sea monster?", "answer": "Kraken"},
	{"question": "Out of the 26 letters in the English alphabet, the most Pokemon begin with which letter?", "answer": "S"},
	{"question": "If it was an actual species, Furret would logically belong to which family of mammals?", "answer": "Mustelidae"},
	{"question": "What was the first word Meowth (of Team Rocket) learned?", "answer": "Rocket"},
	{"question": "What species of flower was Vileplume modeled after?", "answer": "Rafflesia"},
	{"question": "According to Misty, she hates three things. Carrots and bugs are two. Which is the third?", "answer": "peppers"},
	{"question": "Which Pokemon character is named after a legendary Germanic sea siren whose beautiful song lured sailors to their deaths?", "answer": "Lorelei"},
	{"question": "What is the only Pokemon species recognized as having its own distinct verbal language?", "answer": "Jynx"},
	{"question": "Which Pokemon appeared on a wristwatch in one episode of 'The Powerpuff Girls'?", "answer": "Jigglypuff"},
	{"question": "Which Pokemon originally had a six-pointed star on its forehead?", "answer": "Alakazam"},
	{"question": "How many siblings does Brock have?", "answer": "9"},
	{"question": "Kabutops gets its name from...", "answer": "A Japanese war helmet"},
	{"question": "Umbreon gets its name from the Latin word umbra, which means...", "answer": "Shadow"},
	{"question": "Prof. Oak was inspired to become a Pokemon researcher after seeing a fossil of what Pokemon?", "answer": "Omanyte"},
	{"question": "If you lived in Azalea Town, you would most likely love which Pokemon?", "answer": "Slowpoke"},
	{"question": "If you wanted to capture a Snorlax, what Apricorn would you give Kurt to maximize your chances of capturing it?", "answer": "Black Apricorn"},
	{"question": "What city has a 'Mysterious Blue Aura' surrounding it?", "answer": "Cerulean City"},
	{"question": "What is the shortest Pokemon?", "answer": "Diglett"},
	{"question": "Where did Prof. Oak teach before coming to Pallet to start off new trainers?", "answer": "Celadon University"},
	{"question": "Misty's original home is the Cerulean City.", "answer": "true"},
	{"question": "What color was Misty's bike?", "answer": "Orange"},
	{"question": "What color did the Squirtle Squad want to change Misty's hair color to?", "answer": "Purple"},
	{"question": "When Ash goes to get his first Pokemon, who does he originally choose first?", "answer": "Squirtle"},
	{"question": "What was the first Pokemon Ash tried to capture?", "answer": "Pidgey"},
	{"question": "What color is Misty's hairbow?", "answer": "Blue"},
	{"question": "What color are Ash's eyes?", "answer": "Brown"},
	{"question": "What level do Chinchou evolve into Lanturn?", "answer": "Level 27"},
	{"question": "At what level does Squirtle learn Hydro Pump in Pokemon Red/Blue/Yellow?", "answer": "Level 42"},
	{"question": "Can you catch Oddish in 'Pokemon Blue' Game?", "answer": "No"},
	{"question": "What is the name of Ash's father in TV episodes?", "answer": "unknown"},
	{"question": "What is the name of the Pokemon that Brock catches first?", "answer": "Zubat"},
	{"question": "Who beats Ash in the Pokemon League?", "answer": "Ritchie"},
	{"question": "Where does Ash catch a Heracross?", "answer": "Johto"},
	{"question": "What kinds of Pokemon does the Gym Leader of Violet City use?", "answer": "Flying and Normal"},
	{"question": "Name the Pokemon. A Pokemon who sleeps and grows after eating a mountain.", "answer": "Larvitar"},
	{"question": "What is Entei known as?", "answer": "Legendary Dog"},
	{"question": "What is Ash's name in Japanese?", "answer": "Satoshi"},
	{"question": "What is the name of the Game Boy Advance Pokemon game released on 17 March 2003?", "answer": "Ruby"},
	{"question": "Which Pokemon does Tyrogue evolve into if Attack is less than Defense?", "answer": "Hitmonchan"},
	{"question": "What type of Pokemon is Naoshi's Pokemon Subomi?", "answer": "Grass"},
	{"question": "What is the name of James' Pokemon in place of his Victreebel?", "answer": "Masukippa"},
	{"question": "What causes Jigglypuff to sing?", "answer": "Looking into its eyes"},
	{"question": "In Pokemon Blue, what is the first move Jigglypuff learns?", "answer": "Sing"},
	{"question": "Approximately how much does Jigglypuff weigh?", "answer": "12 lbs"},
	{"question": "What can Jigglypuff do to make itself sing longer?", "answer": "Inflate"},
	{"question": "What number is Jigglypuff?", "answer": "39"},
	{"question": "Who's the Boss of Team Rocket?", "answer": "Giovanni"},
	{"question": "Who's Giovanni's mother?", "answer": "Madam Boss"},
	{"question": "What's James' Japanese name?", "answer": "Kojiro"},
	{"question": "What is Jessie's Mother's name?", "answer": "Miyamato"},
	{"question": "In a 'Pokemon Chronicles' episode, where is it shown that Jessie and James first meet?", "answer": "Team Rocket"},
	{"question": "What is Giovanni's Japanese name?", "answer": "Sakaki"},
	{"question": "Which Pokemon can learn all the moves?", "answer": "Mew"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Ash have 30x of?", "answer": "Tauros"},
	{"question": "Which Legendary Pokemon did Ash's Charizard beat?", "answer": "Articuno"},
	{"question": "Which Pokemon is on the Cover of Pokemon Blue?", "answer": "Blastoise"},
	{"question": "Which Pokemon is on the Cover of Pokemon Red?", "answer": "Charizard"},
	{"question": "Which Pokemon is on the Cover of Pokemon Yellow?", "answer": "Pikachu"},
	{"question": "Which Pokemon is on the Cover of Pokemon Green?", "answer": "Venasaur"},
	{"question": "Which Pokemon is on the Cover of Pokemon Silver?", "answer": "Lugia"},
	{"question": "Which Pokemon is on the Cover of Pokemon Gold?", "answer": "Ho-oh"},
	{"question": "Which Pokemon is on the Cover of Pokemon Crystal?", "answer": "Suicine"},
	{"question": "Which Pokemon is on the Cover of Pokemon Ruby?", "answer": "Groudon"},
	{"question": "Which Pokemon is on the Cover of Pokemon Sapphire?", "answer": "Kyogre"},
	{"question": "Which Pokemon is on the Cover of Pokemon Emerald?", "answer": "Rayquaza"},
	{"question": "Which Pokemon is on the Cover of Pokemon Diamond?", "answer": "Dialga"},
	{"question": "Which Pokemon is on the Cover of Pokemon Pearl?", "answer": "Palkia"},
	{"question": "Which Pokemon is on the Cover of Pokemon Platinum?", "answer": "Giratina"},
	{"question": "Which Pokemon is on the Cover of Pokemon Black?", "answer": "Reshiram"},
	{"question": "Which Pokemon is on the Cover of Pokemon White?", "answer": "Zekrom"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon is exclusive in the game Pokemon XD: Gale of Darkness?", "answer": "Shadow Lugia"},
	{"question": "Who is the fire starter in Pokemon Red/Blue?", "answer": "Charmander"},
	{"question": "Who is the water starter in Pokemon Red/Blue?", "answer": "Squirtle"},
	{"question": "Who is the grass starter in Pokemon Red/Blue?", "answer": "Bulbasaur"},
	{"question": "Who is the starter in Pokemon Yellow?", "answer": "Pikachu"},
	{"question": "Who is the fire starter in Pokemon Gold/Silver/Crystal?", "answer": "Cyndaquil"},
	{"question": "Who is the water starter in Pokemon Gold/Silver/Crystal?", "answer": "Totodile"},
	{"question": "Who is the grass starter in Pokemon Gold/Silver/Crystal?", "answer": "Chikorita"},
	{"question": "Who is the fire starter in Pokemon Ruby/Emerald/Sapphire?", "answer": " Torchic"},
	{"question": "Who is the water starter in Pokemon Ruby/Emerald/Sapphire?", "answer": "Mudkip"},
	{"question": "Who is the grass starter in Pokemon Ruby/Emerald/Sapphire?", "answer": "Treecko"},
	{"question": "Who is the fire starter in Pokemon Diamond/Pearl?", "answer": "Chimchar"},
	{"question": "Who is the water starter in Pokemon Diamond/Pearl?", "answer": "Piplup"},
	{"question": "Who is the grass starter in Pokemon Diamond/Pearl?", "answer": "Turtwig"},
	{"question": "Who is the fire starter in Pokemon White/Black?", "answer": "Pokabu"},
	{"question": "Who is the water starter in Pokemon White/Black?", "answer": "Mijumaru"},
	{"question": "Who is the grass starter in Pokemon White/Black?", "answer": "Tsutarja"},
	{"question": "Who is the starter Pokemon in Pokemon Rumble?", "answer": "Rattata"},
	{"question": "Who is the starter Pokemon in Pokemon XD: Gale of Darkness?", "answer": "Eevee"},
	{"question": "Which Pokeball catches Pokemon without fail?", "answer": "Master Ball"},
	{"question": "Which Pokeball allows you to catch Pokemon in the Safari Zone?", "answer": "Safari Ball"},
	{"question": "Which Pokeball works better on Pokémon hooked by a rod?", "answer": "Lure Ball"},
	{"question": "Which Pokeball works better on Pokémon of levels lower than the Pokémon currently in battle?", "answer": "Level Ball"},
	{"question": "Which Pokeball works better on Pokémon that evolve when exposed to radiation from a Moon Stone?", "answer": "Moon Ball"},
	{"question": "Which Pokeball makes a Pokémon more friendly when caught?", "answer": "Friend Ball"},
	{"question": "Which Pokeball works better on Pokémon of the opposite gender?", "answer": "Love Ball"},
	{"question": "Which Pokeball works better on heavier Pokémon?", "answer": "Heavy Ball"},
	{"question": "Which Pokeball works better on fast Pokémon (Generation IV) or Pokémon likely to flee from battle (Generation II)?", "answer": "Fast Ball"},
	{"question": "Which Pokeball allows the player to catch wild Pokémon in the Bug-Catching Contest?", "answer": "Sport Ball"},
	{"question": "Which Pokeball was made in commemoration of some event?", "answer": "Premier Ball"},
	{"question": "Which Pokeball works better on Pokémon whose species have already been caught?", "answer": "Repeat Ball"},
	{"question": "Which Pokeball works better in battles that have lasted longer?", "answer": "Timer Ball"},
	{"question": "Which Pokeball works better on lower-level Pokémon?", "answer": "Nest Ball"},
	{"question": "Which Pokeball works better on Water- and Bug-type Pokémon?", "answer": "Net Ball"},
	{"question": "Which Pokeball works better on Pokémon encountered underwater/while Surfing and fishing?", "answer": "Dive Ball"},
	{"question": "Which Pokeball makes a Pokémon more friendly when caught?", "answer": "Luxury Ball"},
	{"question": "Which Pokeball fully restores a caught Pokémon's HP, PP, and status?", "answer": "Heal Ball"},
	{"question": "Which Pokeball works better when used early in the battle?", "answer": "Quick Ball"},
	{"question": "Which Pokeball works better when used in caves or at night?", "answer": "Dusk Ball"},
	{"question": "Which Pokeball contains an event Pokemon?", "answer": "Cherish Ball"},
	{"question": "Which Pokeball Recatches Pokémon sent through Pal Park?", "answer": "Park Ball"},
	{"question": "What badge do you receive from Pewter City?", "answer": "Boulder Badge"},
	{"question": "What badge do you receive from Cerulean City?", "answer": "Cascade Badge"},
	{"question": "What badge do you receive from Vermilion City?", "answer": "Thunder Badge"},
	{"question": "What badge do you receive from Celadon City?", "answer": "Rainbow Badge"},
	{"question": "What badge do you receive from Fuchsia City?", "answer": "Soul Badge"},
	{"question": "What badge do you receive from Saffron City?", "answer": "Marsh Badge"},
	{"question": "What badge do you receive from Cinnabar Island?", "answer": "Volcano Badge"},
	{"question": "What badge do you receive from Virigian City?", "answer": "Earth Badge"},
	{"question": "What badge do you receive from Mikan Island?", "answer": "Coral-Eye Badge"},
	{"question": "What badge do you receive from Navel Island?", "answer": "Sea Ruby Badge"},
	{"question": "What badge do you receive from Trovita Island?", "answer": "Spike Shell Badge"},
	{"question": "What badge do you receive from Kumquat Island?", "answer": "Jade Star Badge"},
	{"question": "What badge do you receive from Violet City?", "answer": "Zephyr Bade"},
	{"question": "What badge do you receive from Azalea Town?", "answer": "Hive Badge"},
	{"question": "What badge do you receive from Goldenrod City?", "answer": "Plain Badge"},
	{"question": "What badge do you receive from Ecruteak City?", "answer": "Fog Badge"},
	{"question": "What badge do you receive from Cianwood City?", "answer": "Storm Badge"},
	{"question": "What badge do you receive from Olivine City?", "answer": "Mineral Badge"},
	{"question": "What badge do you receive from Mahogany Town?", "answer": "Glacier Badge"},
	{"question": "What badge do you receive from Blackthorn City?", "answer": "Rising Badge"},
	{"question": "What badge do you receive from Rustboro City?", "answer": "Stone Badge"},
	{"question": "What badge do you receive from Dewford Town?", "answer": "Knuckle Badge"},
	{"question": "What badge do you receive from Mauville City?", "answer": "Dynamo Badge"},
	{"question": "What badge do you receive from Lavaridge Town?", "answer": "Heat Badge"},
	{"question": "What badge do you receive from Petalburg City?", "answer": "Balance Badge"},
	{"question": "What badge do you receive from Fortree City?", "answer": "Feather badge"},
	{"question": "What badge do you receive from Mossdeep City?", "answer": "Mind Bade"},
	{"question": "What badge do you receive from Sootopolis City?", "answer": "Rain Badge"},
	{"question": "What badge do you receive from Oreburgh City?", "answer": "Coal Badge"},
	{"question": "What badge do you receive from Eterna City?", "answer": "Forest Badge"},
	{"question": "What badge do you receive from Veilstone City?", "answer": "Cobble Badge"},
	{"question": "What badge do you receive from Pastoria City?", "answer": "Fen Badge"},
	{"question": "What badge do you receive from Heartorne City?", "answer": "Relic Badge"},
	{"question": "What badge do you receive from Canalave City?", "answer": "Mine Badge"},
	{"question": "What badge do you receive from Snowpoint City?", "answer": "Icicle Badge"},
	{"question": "What badge do you receive from Sunyshore City?", "answer": "Beacon Badge"},
	{"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Pewter City?", "answer": "Brock"},
	{"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Cerulean City?", "answer": "Misty"},
	{"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Vermilion City?", "answer": "Lt. Surge"},
	{"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Celadon City?", "answer": "Erika"},
	{"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Fushsia City?", "answer": "Koga"},
	{"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Saffron City?", "answer": "Sabrina"},
	{"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Cinnabar Island?", "answer": "Blaine"},
	{"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Viridian City?", "answer": "Giovanni"},
	{"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Mikan Island?", "answer": "Cissy"},
	{"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Navel Island?", "answer": "Danny"},
	{"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Trovita Island?", "answer": "Rudy"},
	{"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Kumquat Island?", "answer": "Luana"},
	{"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Violet City?", "answer": "Falkner"},
	{"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Azalea Town?", "answer": "Bugsy"},
	{"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Goldenrod City?", "answer": "Whitney"},
	{"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Ecruteak City?", "answer": "Morty"},
	{"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Cianwood City?", "answer": "Chuck"},
	{"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Olivine City?", "answer": "Jasmine"},
	{"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Mahogany Town?", "answer": "Pryce"},
	{"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Blackthorn City?", "answer": "Clair"},
	{"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Rustboro City?", "answer": "Roxanne"},
	{"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Dewford Town?", "answer": "Brawly"},
	{"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Mauville City?", "answer": "Wattson"},
	{"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Lavaridge Town?", "answer": "Flannery"},
	{"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Petarlburg City?", "answer": "Norman"},
	{"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Fortee City?", "answer": "Winona"},
	{"question": "Who are the Gym Leaders of Mossdeep City?", "answer": "Tate and Liza"},
	{"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Sootopolis City?", "answer": "Wallace"},
	{"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Oreburgh City?", "answer": "Roark"},
	{"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Eterna City?", "answer": "Gardenia"},
	{"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Veilstone City?", "answer": "Maylene"},
	{"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Pastoria City?", "answer": "Crasher Wake"},
	{"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Hearthorne City?", "answer": "Fantina"},
	{"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Canalave City?", "answer": "Byron"},
	{"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Snowpoint City?", "answer": "Candice"},
	{"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Sunyshore City?", "answer": "Volkner"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Bulbasaur evolve into?", "answer": "Ivysaur"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Charmander evolve into?", "answer": "Charmeleon"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Squirtle evolve into?", "answer": "Wartortle"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Caterpie evolve into?", "answer": "Metapod"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Weedle evolve into?", "answer": "Kakuna"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Pidgey evolve into?", "answer": "Pidgeotto"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Rattata evolve into?", "answer": "Raticate"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Spearow evolve into?", "answer": "Fearow"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Ekans evolve into?", "answer": "Arbok"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Pichu evolve into?", "answer": "Pikachu"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Sandshrew evolve into?", "answer": "Sandslash"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Nidoran(male) evolve into?", "answer": "Nidorino"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Nidoran(female) evolve into?", "answer": "Nidorina"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Cleffa evolve into?", "answer": "Clefairy"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Vulpix evolve into?", "answer": "Ninetales"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Igglybuff evolve into?", "answer": "Jigglypuff"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Zubat evolve into?", "answer": "Golbat"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Oddish evolve into?", "answer": "Gloom"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Paras evolve into?", "answer": "Parasect"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Venonat evolve into?", "answer": "Venomoth"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Diglett evolve into?", "answer": "Dugtrio"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Meowth evolve into?", "answer": "Persian"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Psyduck evolve into?", "answer": "Golduck"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Mankey evolve into?", "answer": "Primeape"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Growlithe evolve into?", "answer": "Arcanine"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Poliwag evolve into?", "answer": "Poliwhirl"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Abra evolve into?", "answer": "Kadabra"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Machop evolve into?", "answer": "Machoke"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Bellsprout evolve into?", "answer": "Weepinbell"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Tentacool evolve into?", "answer": "Tentacruel"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Geodude evolve into?", "answer": "Graveler"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Ponyta evolve into?", "answer": "Rapidash"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Slowpoke evolve into at level 37?", "answer": "Slowbro"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Slowpoke evolve into when traded holding a King's Rock?", "answer": "Slowking"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Magnemite evolve into?", "answer": "Magneton"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Doduo evolve into?", "answer": "Dodrio"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Seel evolve into?", "answer": "Dewgong"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Grimer evolve into?", "answer": "Muk"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Shellder evolve into?", "answer": "Cloyster"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Gastly evolve into?", "answer": "Haunter"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Onix evolve into?", "answer": "Steelix"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Drowzee evolve into?", "answer": "Hypno"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Krabby evolve into?", "answer": "Kingler"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Voltorb evolve into?", "answer": "Electrode"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Exeggcute evolve into?", "answer": "Exeggutor"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Cubone evolve into?", "answer": "Marowak"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Tyrogue evolve into at level 20 if his attack > defense?", "answer": "Hitmonlee"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Tyrogue evolve into at level 20 if his attack < defense?", "answer": "Hitmonchan"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Tyrogue evolve into at level 20 if his attack = defense?", "answer": "Hitmontop"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Lickitung evolve into?", "answer": "Lickilicky"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Koffing evolve into?", "answer": "Weezing"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Rhyhorn evolve into?", "answer": "Rhydon"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Happiny evolve into?", "answer": "Chansey"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Tangela evolve into?", "answer": "Tangrowth"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Horsea evolve into?", "answer": "Seadra"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Goldeen evolve into?", "answer": "Seaking"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Staryu evolve into?", "answer": "Starmie"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Mime Jr. evolve into?", "answer": "Mr. Mime"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Scyther evolve into?", "answer": "Scizor"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Smoochum evolve into?", "answer": "Jynx"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Elekid evolve into?", "answer": "Electabuzz"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Magby evolve into?", "answer": "Magmar"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Magikarp evolve into?", "answer": "Gyarados"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Eevee evolve into when exposed to a Water Stone?", "answer": "Vaporeon"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Eevee evolve into when exposed to a Thunderstone?", "answer": "Jolteon"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Eevee evolve into when exposed to a Fire Stone?", "answer": "Flareon"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Eevee evolve into when happy durning the daytime?", "answer": "Espeon"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Eevee evolve into when happy durning the nighttime?", "answer": "Umbreon"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Eevee evolve into when leveled up in Eterna Forest?", "answer": "Leafeon"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Eevee evolve into when leveled up on Route 217?", "answer": "Glaceon"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Porygon evolve into?", "answer": "Porygon2"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Omanyte evolve into?", "answer": "Omastar"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Kabuto evolve into?", "answer": "Kabutops"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Munchlax evolve into?", "answer": "Snorlax"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Dratini evolve into?", "answer": "Dragonair"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Chikorita evolve into?", "answer": "Bayleef"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Cyndaquil evolve into?", "answer": "Quilava"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Totodile evolve into?", "answer": "Croconaw"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Sentret evolve into?", "answer": "Furret"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Hoothoot evolve into?", "answer": "Noctowl"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Ledyba evolve into?", "answer": "Ledian"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Spinarak evolve into?", "answer": "Ariados"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Chinchou evolve into?", "answer": "Lanturn"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Togepi evolve into?", "answer": "Togetic"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Natu evolve into?", "answer": "Xatu"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Mareep evolve into?", "answer": "Flaaffy"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Azurill evolve into?", "answer": "Marill"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Bonsly evolve into?", "answer": "Sudowoodo"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Hoppip evolve into?", "answer": "Skiploom"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Aipom evolve into?", "answer": "Ambipom"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Sunkern evolve into?", "answer": "Sunflora"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Yanma evolve into?", "answer": "Yanmega"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Wooper evolve into?", "answer": "Quagsire"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Murkrow evolve into?", "answer": "Honchkrow"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Misdreavus evolve into?", "answer": "Mismagius"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Wynaut evolve into?", "answer": "Wobbuffet"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Pineco evolve into?", "answer": "Forretress"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Gligar evolve into?", "answer": "Gliscor"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Snubbull evolve into?", "answer": "Granbull"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Sneasel evolve into?", "answer": "Weavile"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Teddiursa evolve into?", "answer": "Ursaring"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Slugma evolve into?", "answer": "Magcargo"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Swinub evolve into?", "answer": "Piloswine"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Remoraid evolve into?", "answer": "Octillery"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Mantyke evolve into?", "answer": "Mantine"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Houndour evolve into?", "answer": "Houndoom"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Phanpy evolve into?", "answer": "Donphan"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Larvitar evolve into?", "answer": "Pupitar"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Treecko evolve into?", "answer": "Grovyle"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Torchic evolve into?", "answer": "Combusken"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Mudkip evolve into?", "answer": "Marshtomp"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Poochyena evolve into?", "answer": "Mightyena"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Zigzagoon evolve into?", "answer": "Linoone"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Wurmple evolve into that could evolve into a Beautifly?", "answer": "Silcoon"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Wurmple evolve into that could evolve into a Dustox?", "answer": "Cascoon"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Lotad evolve into?", "answer": "Lombre"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Seedot evolve into?", "answer": "Nuzleaf"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Taillow evolve into?", "answer": "Swellow"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Wingull evolve into?", "answer": "Pelipper"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Ralts evolve into?", "answer": "Kirlia"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Surskit evolve into?", "answer": "Masquerain"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Shroomish evolve into?", "answer": "Breloom"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Slakoth evolve into?", "answer": "Vigoroth"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Nincada evolve into at level 20?", "answer": "Ninjask"},
	{"question": "If Nincada evolves and you have a spare spot in your party and an extra Poke Ball what Pokemon appears in your party?", "answer": "Shedinja"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Whismur evolve into?", "answer": "Loudred"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Makuhita evolve into?", "answer": "Hariyama"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Nosepass evolve into?", "answer": "Probopass"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Skitty evolve into?", "answer": "Delcatty"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Aron evolve into?", "answer": "Lairon"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Meditite evolve into?", "answer": "Medicham"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Electrike evolve into?", "answer": "Manectric"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Budew evolve into?", "answer": "Roselia"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Gulpin evolve into?", "answer": "Swalot"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Carvanha evolve into?", "answer": "Sharpedo"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Wailmer evolve into?", "answer": "Wailord"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Numel evolve into?", "answer": "Camerupt"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Spoink evolve into?", "answer": "Grumpig"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Trapinch evolve into?", "answer": "Vibrava"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Cacnea evolve into?", "answer": "Cacturne"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Swablu evolve into?", "answer": "Altaria"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Barboach evolve into?", "answer": "Whiscash"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Corphish evolve into?", "answer": "Crawdaunt"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Baltoy evolve into?", "answer": "Claydol"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Lileep evolve into?", "answer": "Cradily"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Anorith evolve into?", "answer": "Armaldo"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Feebas evolve into?", "answer": "Milotic"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Shuppet evolve into?", "answer": "Banette"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Duskull evolve into?", "answer": "Dusclops"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Chingling evolve into?", "answer": "Chimecho"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Snorunt evolve into at level 42?", "answer": "Glalie"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Snorunt evolve into if female and exposed to radiation from a Dawn Stone?", "answer": "Froslass"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Spheal evolve into?", "answer": "Sealeo"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Clamperl evolve into when traded holding a DeepSeaTooth?", "answer": "Huntail"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Clamperl evolve into when traded holding a DeepSeaScale?", "answer": "Gorebyss"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Bagon evolve into?", "answer": "Shelgon"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Beldum evolve into?", "answer": "Metang"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Turtwig evolve into?", "answer": "Grotle"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Chimchar evolve into?", "answer": "Monferno"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Piplup evolve into?", "answer": "Prinplup"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Starly evolve into?", "answer": "Staravia"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Bidoof evolve into?", "answer": "Bibarel"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Kricketot evolve into?", "answer": "Kricketune"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Shinx evolve into?", "answer": "Luxio"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Cranidos evolve into?", "answer": "Rampardos"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Shieldon evolve into?", "answer": "Bastiodon"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does a male Burmy evolve into at level 20?", "answer": "Mothim"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does a female Burmy evolve into at level 20?", "answer": "Wormadam"},
	{"question": "What cloak will a Wormadam have if the location where it last battled, right before it evolved was outside or in tall grass?", "answer": "Plant Cloak"},
	{"question": "What cloak will a Wormadam have if the location where it last battled, right before it evolved was in a cave, on a beach, or faced a Pokémon from a Honey tree?", "answer": "Sandy Cloak"},
	{"question": "What cloak will a Wormadam have if the location where it last battled, right before it evolved was outside or in a building?", "answer": "Trash Cloak"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Combee evolve into?", "answer": "Vespiquen"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Buizel evolve into?", "answer": "Floatzel"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Cherubi evolve into?", "answer": "Cherrim"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Shellos evolve into?", "answer": "Gastrodon"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Drifloon evolve into?", "answer": "Drifblim"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Buneary evolve into?", "answer": "Lopunny"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Glameow evolve into?", "answer": "Purugly"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Stunky evolve into?", "answer": "Skuntank"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Bronzor evolve into?", "answer": "Bronzong"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Gible evolve into?", "answer": "Gabite"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Riolu evolve into?", "answer": "Lucario"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Hippopotas evolve into?", "answer": "Hippowdon"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Skorupi evolve into?", "answer": "Drapion"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Croagunk evolve into?", "answer": "Toxicroak"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Finneon evolve into?", "answer": "Lumineon"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Snover evolve into?", "answer": "Abomasnow"},
	{"question": "If Rotom isnt possesing an appliance what form would he be?", "answer": "Normal Rotom"},
	{"question": "If Rotom possessed a Toaster Oven what form would he change to?", "answer": "Heat Rotom"},
	{"question": "If Rotom possessed a Washing Machine what form would he change to?", "answer": "Wash Rotom"},
	{"question": "If Rotom possessed a Refrigerator what form would he change to?", "answer": "Frost Rotom"},
	{"question": "If Rotom possessed a Fan what form would he change to?", "answer": "Fan Rotom"},
	{"question": "If Rotom possessed a Lawnmower what form would he change to?", "answer": "Mow Rotom"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Giratina change into if in Distortion World or holding a Griseous Orb?", "answer": "Origin Form"},
	{"question": "What form does Giratina change into if in the normal Pokemon World?", "answer": "Altered Form"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Ivysaur evolve into?", "answer": "Venusaur"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Charmeleon evolve into?", "answer": "Charizard"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Wartortle evolve into?", "answer": "Blastoise"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Metapod evolve into?", "answer": "Butterfree"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Kakuna evolve into?", "answer": "Beedrill"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Pidgeotto evolve into?", "answer": "Pidgeot"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Pikachu evolve into?", "answer": "Raichu"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Nidorina evolve into?", "answer": "Nidoqueen"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Nidorino evolve into?", "answer": "Nidoking"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Clefairy evolve into?", "answer": "Clefable"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Jigglypuff evolve into?", "answer": "Wigglytuff"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Golbat evolve into?", "answer": "Crobat"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Gloom evolve into when exposed to a Leaf Stone?", "answer": "Vileplume"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Gloom evolve into when exposed to a Sun Stone?", "answer": "Bellossom"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Poliwhirl evolve into when exposed to a Water Stone?", "answer": "Poliwrath"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Poliwhirl evolve into when traded holding a King's Rock?", "answer": "Politoed"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Kadabra evolve into?", "answer": "Alakazam"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Machoke evolve into?", "answer": "Machamp"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Weepinbell evolve into?", "answer": "Victreebel"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Graveler evolve into?", "answer": "Golem"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Magneton evolve into?", "answer": "Magnezone"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Haunter evolve into?", "answer": "Gengar"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Rhydon evolve into?", "answer": "Rhyperior"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Chansey evolve into?", "answer": "Blissey"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Seadra evolve into?", "answer": "Kingdra"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Electabuzz evolve into?", "answer": "Electivire"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Magmar evolve into?", "answer": "Magmortar"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Porygon2 evolve into?", "answer": "Porygon-Z"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Dragonair evolve into?", "answer": "Dragonite"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Bayleef evolve into?", "answer": "Meganium"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Quilava evolve into?", "answer": "Typhlosion"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Croconaw evolve into?", "answer": "Feraligatr"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Togetic evolve into?", "answer": "Togekiss"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Flaaffy evolve into?", "answer": "Ampharos"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Marill evolve into?", "answer": "Azumarill"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Skiploom evolve into?", "answer": "Jumpluff"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Piloswine evolve into?", "answer": "Mamoswine"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Pupitar evolve into?", "answer": "Tyranitar"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Grovyle evolve into?", "answer": "Sceptile"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Combusken evolve into?", "answer": "Blaziken"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Marshtomp evolve into?", "answer": "Swampert"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Silcoon evolve into?", "answer": "Beautifly"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Cascoon evolve into?", "answer": "Dustox"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Lombre evolve into?", "answer": "Ludicolo"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Nuzleaf evolve into?", "answer": "Shiftry"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Kirlia evolve into at level 30?", "answer": "Gardevoir"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Kirlia evolve into if male and exposed to radiation from a Dawn Stone?", "answer": "Gallade"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Vigoroth evolve into?", "answer": "Slaking"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Loudred evolve into?", "answer": "Exploud"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Lairon evolve into?", "answer": "Aggron"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Roselia evolve into?", "answer": "Roserade"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Vibrava evolve into?", "answer": "Flygon"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Dusclops evolve into?", "answer": "Dusknoir"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Sealeo evolve into?", "answer": "Walrein"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Shelgon evolve into?", "answer": "Salamence"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Metang evolve into?", "answer": "Metagross"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Grotle evolve into?", "answer": "Torterra"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Monferno evolve into?", "answer": "Infernape"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Prinplup evolve into?", "answer": "Empoleon"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Staravia evolve into?", "answer": "Staraptor"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Luxio evolve into?", "answer": "Luxray"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Gabite evolve into?", "answer": "Garchomp"},
	{"question": "What are Bulbasaur's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass  and  Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Ivysaur's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass  and  Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Venusaur's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Charmander's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
	{"question": "What are Charmeleon's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
	{"question": "What are Charizard's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Squirtle's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Wartortle's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Blastoise's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Caterpie's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug"},
	{"question": "What are Metapod's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug"},
	{"question": "What are Butterfree's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Weedle's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Kakuna's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Beedrill's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Pidgey's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Pidgeotto's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Pidgeot's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Rattata's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Raticate's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Spearow's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Fearow's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Ekans's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Arbok's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Pikachu's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
	{"question": "What are Raichu's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
	{"question": "What are Sandshrew's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Sandslash's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Nidoran[male]'s type(s)?", "answer": "Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Nidorina's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Nidoqueen's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison and Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Nidoran[female]'s type(s)?", "answer": "Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Nidorino's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Nidoking's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison and Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Clefairy's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Clefable's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Vulpix's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
	{"question": "What are Ninetales's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
	{"question": "What are Jigglypuff's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Wigglytuff's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Zubat's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Golbat's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Oddish's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Gloom's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Vileplume's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Paras's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Grass"},
	{"question": "What are Parasect's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Grass"},
	{"question": "What are Venonat's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Venomoth's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Diglett's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Dugtrio's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Meowth's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Persian's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Psyduck's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Golduck's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Mankey's type(s)?", "answer": "Fighting"},
	{"question": "What are Primeape's type(s)?", "answer": "Fighting"},
	{"question": "What are Growlithe's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
	{"question": "What are Arcanine's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
	{"question": "What are Poliwag's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Poliwhirl's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Poliwrath's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Fighting"},
	{"question": "What are Abra's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Kadabra's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Alakazam's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Machop's type(s)?", "answer": "Fighting"},
	{"question": "What are Machoke's type(s)?", "answer": "Fighting"},
	{"question": "What are Machamp's type(s)?", "answer": "Fighting"},
	{"question": "What are Bellsprout's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Weepinbell's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Victreebel's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Tentacool's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Tentacruel's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Geodude's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Graveler's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Golem's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Ponyta's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
	{"question": "What are Rapidash's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
	{"question": "What are Slowpoke's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Slowbro's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Magnemite's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric and Steel"},
	{"question": "What are Magneton's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric and Steel"},
	{"question": "What are Farfetch'd's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Doduo's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Dodrio's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Seel's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Dewgong's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Ice"},
	{"question": "What are Grimer's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Muk's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Shellder's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Cloyster's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Ice"},
	{"question": "What are Gastly's type(s)?", "answer": "Ghost and Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Haunter's type(s)?", "answer": "Ghost and Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Gengar's type(s)?", "answer": "Ghost and Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Onix's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Drowzee's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Hypno's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Krabby's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Kingler's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Voltorb's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
	{"question": "What are Electrode's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
	{"question": "What are Exeggcute's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Exeggutor's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Cubone's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Marowak's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Hitmonlee's type(s)?", "answer": "Fighting"},
	{"question": "What are Hitmonchan's type(s)?", "answer": "Fighting"},
	{"question": "What are Lickitung's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Koffing's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Weezing's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Rhyhorn's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground and Rock"},
	{"question": "What are Rhydon's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground and Rock"},
	{"question": "What are Chansey's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Tangela's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
	{"question": "What are Kangaskhan's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Horsea's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Seadra's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Goldeen's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Seaking's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Staryu's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Starmie's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Mr. Mime's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Scyther's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Jynx's type(s)?", "answer": "Ice and Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Electabuzz's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
	{"question": "What are Magmar's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
	{"question": "What are Pinsir's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug"},
	{"question": "What are Tauros's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Magikarp's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Gyarados's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Lapras's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Ice"},
	{"question": "What are Ditto's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Eevee's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Vaporeon's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Jolteon's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
	{"question": "What are Flareon's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
	{"question": "What are Porygon's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Omanyte's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Water"},
	{"question": "What are Omastar's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Water"},
	{"question": "What are Kabuto's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Water"},
	{"question": "What are Kabutops's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Water"},
	{"question": "What are Aerodactyl's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Snorlax's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Articuno's type(s)?", "answer": "Ice and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Zapdos's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Moltres's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Dratini's type(s)?", "answer": "Dragon"},
	{"question": "What are Dragonair's type(s)?", "answer": "Dragon"},
	{"question": "What are Dragonite's type(s)?", "answer": "Dragon and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Mewtwo's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Mew's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Chikorita's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
	{"question": "What are Bayleef's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
	{"question": "What are Meganium's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
	{"question": "What are Cyndaquil's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
	{"question": "What are Quilava's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
	{"question": "What are Typhlosion's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
	{"question": "What are Totodile's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Croconaw's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Feraligatr's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Sentret's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Furret's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Hoothoot's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Noctowl's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Ledyba's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Ledian's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Spinarak's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Ariados's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Crobat's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Chinchou's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Electric"},
	{"question": "What are Lanturn's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Electric"},
	{"question": "What are Pichu's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
	{"question": "What are Cleffa's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Igglybuff's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Togepi's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Togetic's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Natu's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Xatu's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Mareep's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
	{"question": "What are Flaaffy's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
	{"question": "What are Ampharos's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
	{"question": "What are Bellossom's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
	{"question": "What are Marill's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Azumarill's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Sudowoodo's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock"},
	{"question": "What are Politoed's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Hoppip's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Skiploom's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Jumpluff's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Aipom's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Sunkern's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
	{"question": "What are Sunflora's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
	{"question": "What are Yanma's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Wooper's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Quagsire's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Espeon's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Umbreon's type(s)?", "answer": "Dark"},
	{"question": "What are Murkrow's type(s)?", "answer": "Dark and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Slowking's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Misdreavus's type(s)?", "answer": "Ghost"},
	{"question": "What are Unown's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Wobbuffet's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Girafarig's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Pineco's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug"},
	{"question": "What are Forretress's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Steel"},
	{"question": "What are Dunsparce's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Gligar's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Steelix's type(s)?", "answer": "Steel and Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Snubbull's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Granbull's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Qwilfish's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Scizor's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Steel"},
	{"question": "What are Shuckle's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Rock"},
	{"question": "What are Heracross's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Fighting"},
	{"question": "What are Sneasel's type(s)?", "answer": "Dark and Ice"},
	{"question": "What are Teddiursa's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Ursaring's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Slugma's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
	{"question": "What are Magcargo's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire and Rock"},
	{"question": "What are Swinub's type(s)?", "answer": "Ice and Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Piloswine's type(s)?", "answer": "Ice and Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Corsola's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Rock"},
	{"question": "What are Remoraid's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Octillery's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Delibird's type(s)?", "answer": "Ice and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Mantine's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Skarmory's type(s)?", "answer": "Steel and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Houndour's type(s)?", "answer": "Dark and Fire"},
	{"question": "What are Houndoom's type(s)?", "answer": "Dark and Fire"},
	{"question": "What are Kingdra's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Dragon"},
	{"question": "What are Phanpy's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Donphan's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Porygon2's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Stantler's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Smeargle's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Tyrogue's type(s)?", "answer": "Fighting"},
	{"question": "What are Hitmontop's type(s)?", "answer": "Fighting"},
	{"question": "What are Smoochum's type(s)?", "answer": "Ice and Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Elekid's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
	{"question": "What are Magby's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
	{"question": "What are Miltank's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Blissey's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Raikou's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
	{"question": "What are Entei's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
	{"question": "What are Suicune's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Larvitar's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Pupitar's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Tyranitar's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Dark"},
	{"question": "What are Lugia's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Ho-Oh's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Celebi's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic and Grass"},
	{"question": "What are Treecko's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
	{"question": "What are Grovyle's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
	{"question": "What are Sceptile's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
	{"question": "What are Torchic's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
	{"question": "What are Combusken's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire and Fighting"},
	{"question": "What are Blaziken's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire and Fighting"},
	{"question": "What are Mudkip's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Marshtomp's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Swampert's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Poochyena's type(s)?", "answer": "Dark"},
	{"question": "What are Mightyena's type(s)?", "answer": "Dark"},
	{"question": "What are Zigzagoon's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Linoone's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Wurmple's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug"},
	{"question": "What are Silcoon's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug"},
	{"question": "What are Beautifly's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Cascoon's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug"},
	{"question": "What are Dustox's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Lotad's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Grass"},
	{"question": "What are Lombre's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Grass"},
	{"question": "What are Ludicolo's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Grass"},
	{"question": "What are Seedot's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
	{"question": "What are Nuzleaf's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Dark"},
	{"question": "What are Shiftry's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Dark"},
	{"question": "What are Taillow's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Swellow's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Wingull's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Pelipper's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Ralts's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Kirlia's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Gardevoir's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Surskit's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Water"},
	{"question": "What are Masquerain's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Shroomish's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
	{"question": "What are Breloom's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Fighting"},
	{"question": "What are Slakoth's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Vigoroth's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Slaking's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Nincada's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Ninjask's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Shedinja's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Ghost"},
	{"question": "What are Whismur's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Loudred's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Exploud's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Makuhita's type(s)?", "answer": "Fighting"},
	{"question": "What are Hariyama's type(s)?", "answer": "Fighting"},
	{"question": "What are Azurill's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Nosepass's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock"},
	{"question": "What are Skitty's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Delcatty's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Sableye's type(s)?", "answer": "Dark and Ghost"},
	{"question": "What are Mawile's type(s)?", "answer": "Steel"},
	{"question": "What are Aron's type(s)?", "answer": "Steel and Rock"},
	{"question": "What are Lairon's type(s)?", "answer": "Steel and Rock"},
	{"question": "What are Aggron's type(s)?", "answer": "Steel and Rock"},
	{"question": "What are Meditite's type(s)?", "answer": "Fighting and Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Medicham's type(s)?", "answer": "Fighting and Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Electrike's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
	{"question": "What are Manectric's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
	{"question": "What are Plusle's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
	{"question": "What are Minun's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
	{"question": "What are Volbeat's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug"},
	{"question": "What are Illumise's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug"},
	{"question": "What are Roselia's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Gulpin's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Swalot's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Carvanha's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Dark"},
	{"question": "What are Sharpedo's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Dark"},
	{"question": "What are Wailmer's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Wailord's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Numel's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire and Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Camerupt's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire and Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Torkoal's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
	{"question": "What are Spoink's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Grumpig's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Spinda's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Trapinch's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Vibrava's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground and Dragon"},
	{"question": "What are Flygon's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground and Dragon"},
	{"question": "What are Cacnea's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
	{"question": "What are Cacturne's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Dark"},
	{"question": "What are Swablu's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Altaria's type(s)?", "answer": "Dragon and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Zangoose's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Seviper's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Lunatone's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Solrock's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Barboach's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Whiscash's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Corphish's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Crawdaunt's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Dark"},
	{"question": "What are Baltoy's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground and Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Claydol's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground and Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Lileep's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Grass"},
	{"question": "What are Cradily's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Grass"},
	{"question": "What are Anorith's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Bug"},
	{"question": "What are Armaldo's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Bug"},
	{"question": "What are Feebas's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Milotic's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Castform's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Kecleon's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Shuppet's type(s)?", "answer": "Ghost"},
	{"question": "What are Banette's type(s)?", "answer": "Ghost"},
	{"question": "What are Duskull's type(s)?", "answer": "Ghost"},
	{"question": "What are Dusclops's type(s)?", "answer": "Ghost"},
	{"question": "What are Tropius's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Chimecho's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Absol's type(s)?", "answer": "Dark"},
	{"question": "What are Wynaut's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Snorunt's type(s)?", "answer": "Ice"},
	{"question": "What are Glalie's type(s)?", "answer": "Ice"},
	{"question": "What are Spheal's type(s)?", "answer": "Ice and Water"},
	{"question": "What are Sealeo's type(s)?", "answer": "Ice and Water"},
	{"question": "What are Walrein's type(s)?", "answer": "Ice and Water"},
	{"question": "What are Clamperl's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Huntail's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Gorebyss's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Relicanth's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Rock"},
	{"question": "What are Luvdisc's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Bagon's type(s)?", "answer": "Dragon"},
	{"question": "What are Shelgon's type(s)?", "answer": "Dragon"},
	{"question": "What are Salamence's type(s)?", "answer": "Dragon and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Beldum's type(s)?", "answer": "Steel and Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Metang's type(s)?", "answer": "Steel and Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Metagross's type(s)?", "answer": "Steel and Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Regirock's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock"},
	{"question": "What are Regice's type(s)?", "answer": "Ice"},
	{"question": "What are Registeel's type(s)?", "answer": "Steel"},
	{"question": "What are Latias's type(s)?", "answer": "Dragon and Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Latios's type(s)?", "answer": "Dragon and Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Kyogre's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Groudon's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Rayquaza's type(s)?", "answer": "Dragon and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Jirachi's type(s)?", "answer": "Steel and Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Deoxys [Normal Form]'s type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Deoxys [Attack Form]'s type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Deoxys [Defense Form]'s type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Deoxys [Speed Form]'s type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Turtwig's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
	{"question": "What are Grotle's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
	{"question": "What are Torterra's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Chimchar's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
	{"question": "What are Monferno's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire and Fighting"},
	{"question": "What are Infernape's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire and Fighting"},
	{"question": "What are Piplup's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Prinplup's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Empoleon's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Steel"},
	{"question": "What are Starly's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Staravia's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Staraptor's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Bidoof's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Bibarel's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Water"},
	{"question": "What are Kricketot's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug"},
	{"question": "What are Kricketune's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug"},
	{"question": "What are Shinx's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
	{"question": "What are Luxio's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
	{"question": "What are Luxray's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
	{"question": "What are Budew's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and "},
	{"question": "What are Roserade's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Poison"},
	{"question": "What are Cranidos's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock"},
	{"question": "What are Rampardos's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock"},
	{"question": "What are Shieldon's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Steel"},
	{"question": "What are Bastiodon's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Steel"},
	{"question": "What are Burmy's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug"},
	{"question": "What two types are Plant Cloak Wormadam?", "answer": "Bug and Grass"},
	{"question": "What two types are Sandy Cloak Wormadam?", "answer": "Bug and Ground"},
	{"question": "What two types are Trash Cloak Wormadam?", "answer": "Bug and Steel"},
	{"question": "What are Mothim's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Combee's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Vespiquen's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Pachirisu's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
	{"question": "What are Buizel's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Floatzel's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Cherubi's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
	{"question": "What are Cherrim's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
	{"question": "What are Shellos's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Gastrodon's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Ambipom's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Drifloon's type(s)?", "answer": "Ghost and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Drifblim's type(s)?", "answer": "Ghost and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Buneary's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Lopunny's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Mismagius's type(s)?", "answer": "Ghost"},
	{"question": "What are Honchkrow's type(s)?", "answer": "Dark and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Glameow's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Purugly's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Chingling's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Stunky's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison and Dark"},
	{"question": "What are Skuntank's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison and Dark"},
	{"question": "What are Bronzor's type(s)?", "answer": "Steel and Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Bronzong's type(s)?", "answer": "Steel and Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Bonsly's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock"},
	{"question": "What are Mime Jr.'s type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Happiny's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Chatot's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Spiritomb's type(s)?", "answer": "Ghost and Dark"},
	{"question": "What are Gible's type(s)?", "answer": "Dragon and Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Gabite's type(s)?", "answer": "Dragon and Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Garchomp's type(s)?", "answer": "Dragon and Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Munchlax's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Riolu's type(s)?", "answer": "Fighting"},
	{"question": "What are Lucario's type(s)?", "answer": "Fighting and Steel"},
	{"question": "What are Hippopotas's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Hippowdon's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Skorupi's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison and Bug"},
	{"question": "What are Drapion's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison and Dark"},
	{"question": "What are Croagunk's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison and Fighting"},
	{"question": "What are Toxicroak's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison and Fighting"},
	{"question": "What are Carnivine's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
	{"question": "What are Finneon's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Lumineon's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Mantyke's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Snover's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Ice"},
	{"question": "What are Abomasnow's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Ice"},
	{"question": "What are Weavile's type(s)?", "answer": "Dark and Ice"},
	{"question": "What are Magnezone's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric and Steel"},
	{"question": "What are Lickilicky's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Rhyperior's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground and Rock"},
	{"question": "What are Tangrowth's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
	{"question": "What are Electivire's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
	{"question": "What are Magmortar's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
	{"question": "What are Togekiss's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Yanmega's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Leafeon's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
	{"question": "What are Glaceon's type(s)?", "answer": "Ice"},
	{"question": "What are Gliscor's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Mamoswine's type(s)?", "answer": "Ice and Ground"},
	{"question": "What are Porygon-Z's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Gallade's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic and Fighting"},
	{"question": "What are Probopass's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Steel"},
	{"question": "What are Dusknoir's type(s)?", "answer": "Ghost"},
	{"question": "What are Froslass's type(s)?", "answer": "Ice and Ghost"},
	{"question": "What are Heat Rotom's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric and Ghost"},
	{"question": "What are Wash Rotom's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric and Ghost"},
	{"question": "What are Frost Rotom's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric and Ghost"},
	{"question": "What are Fan Rotom's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric and Ghost"},
	{"question": "What are Mow Rotom's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric and Ghost"},
	{"question": "What are Rotom's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric and Ghost"},
	{"question": "What are Uxie's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Mesprit's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Azelf's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Dialga's type(s)?", "answer": "Steel and Dragon"},
	{"question": "What are Palkia's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Dragon"},
	{"question": "What are Heatran's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire and Steel"},
	{"question": "What are Regigigas's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What are Giratina's type(s)?", "answer": "Ghost and Dragon"},
	{"question": "What are Giratina's type(s)?", "answer": "Ghost and Dragon"},
	{"question": "What are Cresselia's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
	{"question": "What are Phione's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Manaphy's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
	{"question": "What are Darkrai's type(s)?", "answer": "Dark"},
	{"question": "What are Shaymin's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
	{"question": "What are Shaymin's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Flying"},
	{"question": "What are Arceus's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Ivysaur evolve from?", "answer": "Bulbasaur"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Charmeleon evolve from?", "answer": "Charmander"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Wartortle evolve from?", "answer": "Squirtle"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Metapod evolve from?", "answer": "Caterpie"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Kakuna evolve from?", "answer": "Weedle"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Pidgeotto evolve from?", "answer": "Pidgey"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Raticate evolve from?", "answer": "Rattata"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Fearow evolve from?", "answer": "Spearow"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Arbok evolve from?", "answer": "Ekans"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Pikachu evolve from?", "answer": "Pichu"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Sandslash evolve from?", "answer": "Sandshrew"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Nidorina evolve from?", "answer": "Nidoran(male)"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Nidorino evolve from?", "answer": "Nidoran(female)"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Clefairy evolve from?", "answer": "Cleffa"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Ninetales evolve from?", "answer": "Vulpix"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Jigglypuff evolve from?", "answer": "Igglybuff"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Golbat evolve from?", "answer": "Zubat"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Gloom evolve from?", "answer": "Oddish"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Parasect evolve from?", "answer": "Paras"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Venomoth evolve from?", "answer": "Venonat"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Dugtrio evolve from?", "answer": "Diglett"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Persian evolve from?", "answer": "Meowth"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Golduck evolve from?", "answer": "Psyduck"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Primeape evolve from?", "answer": "Mankey"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Arcanine evolve from?", "answer": "Growlithe"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Poliwhirl evolve from?", "answer": "Poliwag"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Kadabra evolve from?", "answer": "Abra"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Machoke evolve from?", "answer": "Machop"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Weepinbell evolve from?", "answer": "Bellsprout"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Tentacruel evolve from?", "answer": "Tentacool"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Graveler evolve from?", "answer": "Geodude"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Rapidash evolve from?", "answer": "Ponyta"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Slowbro evolve from?", "answer": "Slowpoke"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Slowking evolve from?", "answer": "Slowpoke"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Magneton evolve from?", "answer": "Magnemite"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Dodrio evolve from?", "answer": "Doduo"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Dewgong evolve from?", "answer": "Seel"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Muk evolve from?", "answer": "Grimer"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Cloyster evolve from?", "answer": "Shellder"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Haunter evolve from?", "answer": "Gastly"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Steelix evolve from?", "answer": "Onix"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Hypno evolve from?", "answer": "Drowzee"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Kingler evolve from?", "answer": "Krabby"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Electrode evolve from?", "answer": "Voltorb"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Exeggutor evolve from?", "answer": "Exeggcute"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Marowak evolve from?", "answer": "Cubone"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Hitmonlee evolve from?", "answer": "Tyrogue"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Hitmonchan evolve from?", "answer": "Tyrogue"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Hitmontop evolve from?", "answer": "Tyrogue"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Lickilicky evolve from?", "answer": "Lickitung"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Weezing evolve from?", "answer": "Koffing"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Rhydon evolve from?", "answer": "Rhyhorn"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Chansey evolve from?", "answer": "Happiny"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Tangrowth evolve from?", "answer": "Tangela"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Seadra evolve from?", "answer": "Horsea"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Seaking evolve from?", "answer": "Goldeen"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Starmie evolve from?", "answer": "Staryu"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Mr. Mime evolve from?", "answer": "Mime Jr."},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Scizor evolve from?", "answer": "Scyther"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Jynx evolve from?", "answer": "Smoochum"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Electabuzz evolve from?", "answer": "Elekid"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Magmar evolve from?", "answer": "Magby"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Gyarados evolve from?", "answer": "Magikarp"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Vaporeon evolve from?", "answer": "Eevee"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Jolteon evolve from?", "answer": "Eevee"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Flareon evolve from?", "answer": "Eevee"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Espeon evolve from?", "answer": "Eevee"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Umbreon evolve from?", "answer": "Eevee"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Leafeon evolve from?", "answer": "Eevee"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Glaceon evolve from?", "answer": "Eevee"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Porygon2 evolve from?", "answer": "Porygon"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Omastar evolve from?", "answer": "Omanyte"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Kabutops evolve from?", "answer": "Kabuto"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Snorlax evolve from?", "answer": "Munchlax"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Dragonair evolve from?", "answer": "Dratini"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Bayleef evolve from?", "answer": "Chikorita"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Quilava evolve from?", "answer": "Cyndaquil"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Croconaw evolve from?", "answer": "Totodile"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Furret evolve from?", "answer": "Sentret"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Noctowl evolve from?", "answer": "Hoothoot"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Ledian evolve from?", "answer": "Ledyba"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Ariados evolve from?", "answer": "Spinarak"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Lanturn evolve from?", "answer": "Chinchou"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Togetic evolve from?", "answer": "Togepi"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Xatu evolve from?", "answer": "Natu"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Flaaffy evolve from?", "answer": "Mareep"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Marill evolve from?", "answer": "Azurill"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Sudowoodo evolve from?", "answer": "Bonsly"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Skiploom evolve from?", "answer": "Hoppip"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Ambipom evolve from?", "answer": "Aipom"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Sunflora evolve from?", "answer": "Sunkern"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Yanmega evolve from?", "answer": "Yanma"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Quagsire evolve from?", "answer": "Wooper"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Honchkrow evolve from?", "answer": "Murkrow"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Mismagius evolve from?", "answer": "Misdreavus"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Wobbuffet evolve from?", "answer": "Wynaut"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Forretress evolve from?", "answer": "Pineco"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Gliscor evolve from?", "answer": "Gligar"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Granbull evolve from?", "answer": "Snubbull"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Weavile evolve from?", "answer": "Sneasel"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Ursaring evolve from?", "answer": "Teddiursa"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Magcargo evolve from?", "answer": "Slugma"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Piloswine evolve from?", "answer": "Swinub"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Octillery evolve from?", "answer": "Remoraid"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Mantine evolve from?", "answer": "Mantyke"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Houndoom evolve from?", "answer": "Houndour"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Donphan evolve from?", "answer": "Phanpy"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Pupitar evolve from?", "answer": "Larvitar"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Grovyle evolve from?", "answer": "Treecko"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Combusken evolve from?", "answer": "Torchic"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Marshtomp evolve from?", "answer": "Mudkip"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Mightyena evolve from?", "answer": "Poochyena"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Linoone evolve from?", "answer": "Zigzagoon"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Silcoon evolve from?", "answer": "Wurmple"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Cascoon evolve from?", "answer": "Wurmple"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Lombre evolve from?", "answer": "Lotad"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Nuzleaf evolve from?", "answer": "Seedot"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Swellow evolve from?", "answer": "Taillow"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Pelipper evolve from?", "answer": "Wingull"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Kirlia evolve from?", "answer": "Ralts"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Masquerain evolve from?", "answer": "Surskit"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Breloom evolve from?", "answer": "Shroomish"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Vigoroth evolve from?", "answer": "Slakoth"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Ninjask evolve from?", "answer": "Nincada"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Shedinja evolve from?", "answer": "Nincada"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Loudred evolve from?", "answer": "Whismur"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Hariyama evolve from?", "answer": "Makuhita"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Probopass evolve from?", "answer": "Nosepass"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Delcatty evolve from?", "answer": "Skitty"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Lairon evolve from?", "answer": "Aron"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Medicham evolve from?", "answer": "Meditite"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Manectric evolve from?", "answer": "Electrike"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Roselia evolve from?", "answer": "Budew"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Swalot evolve from?", "answer": "Gulpin"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Sharpedo evolve from?", "answer": "Carvanha"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Wailord evolve from?", "answer": "Wailmer"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Camerupt evolve from?", "answer": "Numel"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Grumpig evolve from?", "answer": "Spoink"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Vibrava evolve from?", "answer": "Trapinch"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Cacturne evolve from?", "answer": "Cacnea"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Altaria evolve from?", "answer": "Swablu"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Whiscash evolve from?", "answer": "Barboach"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Crawdaunt evolve from?", "answer": "Corphish"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Claydol evolve from?", "answer": "Baltoy"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Cradily evolve from?", "answer": "Lileep"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Armaldo evolve from?", "answer": "Anorith"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Milotic evolve from?", "answer": "Feebas"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Banette evolve from?", "answer": "Shuppet"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Dusclops evolve from?", "answer": "Duskull"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Chimecho evolve from?", "answer": "Chingling"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Glalie evolve from?", "answer": "Snorunt"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Froslass evolve from?", "answer": "Snorunt"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Sealeo evolve from?", "answer": "Spheal"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Huntail evolve from?", "answer": "Clamperl"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Gorebyss evolve from?", "answer": "Clamperl"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Shelgon evolve from?", "answer": "Bagon"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Metang evolve from?", "answer": "Beldum"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Grotle evolve from?", "answer": "Turtwig"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Monferno evolve from?", "answer": "Chimchar"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Prinplup evolve from?", "answer": "Piplup"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Staravia evolve from?", "answer": "Starly"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Bibarel evolve from?", "answer": "Bidoof"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Kricketune evolve from?", "answer": "Kricketot"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Luxio evolve from?", "answer": "Shinx"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Rampardos evolve from?", "answer": "Cranidos"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Bastiodon evolve from?", "answer": "Shieldon"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Wormadam evolve from?", "answer": "Burmy"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Mothim evolve from?", "answer": "Burmy"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Vespiquen evolve from?", "answer": "Combee"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Floatzel evolve from?", "answer": "Buizel"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Cherrim evolve from?", "answer": "Cherubi"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Gastrodon evolve from?", "answer": "Shellos"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Drifblim evolve from?", "answer": "Drifloon"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Lopunny evolve from?", "answer": "Buneary"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Purugly evolve from?", "answer": "Glameow"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Skuntank evolve from?", "answer": "Stunky"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Bronzong evolve from?", "answer": "Bronzor"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Gabite evolve from?", "answer": "Gible"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Lucario evolve from?", "answer": "Riolu"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Hippowdon evolve from?", "answer": "Hippopotas"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Drapion evolve from?", "answer": "Skorupi"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Toxicroak evolve from?", "answer": "Croagunk"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Lumineon evolve from?", "answer": "Finneon"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Abomasnow evolve from?", "answer": "Snover"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Venusaur evolve from?", "answer": "Ivysaur"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Charizard evolve from?", "answer": "Charmeleon"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Blastoise evolve from?", "answer": "Wartortle"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Butterfree evolve from?", "answer": "Metapod"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Beedrill evolve from?", "answer": "Kakuna"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Pidgeot evolve from?", "answer": "Pidgeotto"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Raichu evolve from?", "answer": "Pikachu"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Nidoqueen evolve from?", "answer": "Nidorina"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Nidoking evolve from?", "answer": "Nidorino"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Clefable evolve from?", "answer": "Clefairy"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Wigglytuff evolve from?", "answer": "Jigglypuff"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Crobat evolve from?", "answer": "Golbat"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Vileplume evolve from?", "answer": "Gloom"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Bellossom evolve from?", "answer": "Gloom"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Poliwrath evolve from?", "answer": "Poliwhirl"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Politoed evolve from?", "answer": "Poliwhirl"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Alakazam evolve from?", "answer": "Kadabra"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Machamp evolve from?", "answer": "Machoke"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Victreebel evolve from?", "answer": "Weepinbell"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Golem evolve from?", "answer": "Graveler"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Magnezone evolve from?", "answer": "Magneton"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Gengar evolve from?", "answer": "Haunter"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Rhyperior evolve from?", "answer": "Rhydon"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Blissey evolve from?", "answer": "Chansey"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Kingdra evolve from?", "answer": "Seadra"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Electivire evolve from?", "answer": "Electabuzz"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Magmortar evolve from?", "answer": "Magmar"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Porygon-Z evolve from?", "answer": "Porygon2"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Dragonite evolve from?", "answer": "Dragonair"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Meganium evolve from?", "answer": "Bayleef"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Typhlosion evolve from?", "answer": "Quilava"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Feraligatr evolve from?", "answer": "Croconaw"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Togekiss evolve from?", "answer": "Togetic"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Ampharos evolve from?", "answer": "Flaaffy"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Azumarill evolve from?", "answer": "Marill"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Jumpluff evolve from?", "answer": "Skiploom"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Mamoswine evolve from?", "answer": "Piloswine"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Tyranitar evolve from?", "answer": "Pupitar"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Sceptile evolve from?", "answer": "Grovyle"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Blaziken evolve from?", "answer": "Combusken"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Swampert evolve from?", "answer": "Marshtomp"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Beautifly evolve from?", "answer": "Silcoon"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Dustox evolve from?", "answer": "Cascoon"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Ludicolo evolve from?", "answer": "Lombre"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Shiftry evolve from?", "answer": "Nuzleaf"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Gardevoir evolve from?", "answer": "Kirlia"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Gallade evolve from?", "answer": "Kirlia"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Slaking evolve from?", "answer": "Vigoroth"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Exploud evolve from?", "answer": "Loudred"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Aggron evolve from?", "answer": "Lairon"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Roserade evolve from?", "answer": "Roselia"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Flygon evolve from?", "answer": "Vibrava"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Dusknoir evolve from?", "answer": "Dusclops"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Walrein evolve from?", "answer": "Sealeo"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Salamence evolve from?", "answer": "Shelgon"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Metagross evolve from?", "answer": "Metang"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Torterra evolve from?", "answer": "Grotle"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Infernape evolve from?", "answer": "Monferno"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Empoleon evolve from?", "answer": "Prinplup"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Staraptor evolve from?", "answer": "Staravia"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Luxray evolve from?", "answer": "Luxio"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon does Garchomp evolve from?", "answer": "Gabite"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon are known as The Legendary birds?", "answer": "Articuno Zapdos and Moltres"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon are known as The Mew Duo?", "answer": "Mewtwo and Mew"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon are known as The Legendary Beasts?", "answer": "Raikou Entei and Suicune"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon are known as The Tower Duo?", "answer": "Lugia and Ho-Oh"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon are known as The Legendary Golems?", "answer": "Regirock Regice and Registeel"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon are known as The Eon duo?", "answer": "Latias and Latios"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon are known as The Weather Trio?", "answer": "Kyogre Groudon and Rayquaza"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon are known as The Lake guardians?", "answer": "Uxie Mesprit and Azelf"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon are known as The Legendary dragons?", "answer": "Dialga Palkia and Giratina"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon are known as The Lunar duo?", "answer": "Cresselia and Darkrai"},
	{"question": "What Pokemon are known as The Sea guardians?", "answer": "Phione and Manaphy"},
	{"question": "Articuno, Zapdos, and Moltres are known as...?", "answer": "The Legendary birds"},
	{"question": "Mewtwo, and Mew are known as...?", "answer": "The Mew Duo"},
	{"question": "Raikou, Entei, and Suicune are known as...?", "answer": "The Legendary Beasts"},
	{"question": "Lugia, and Ho-Oh are known as...?", "answer": "The Tower Duo"},
	{"question": "Regirock, Regice, and Registeel are known as...?", "answer": "The Legendary Golems"},
	{"question": "Latias, and Latios are known as...?", "answer": "The Eon duo"},
	{"question": "Kyogre, Groudon, and Rayquaza are known as...?", "answer": "The Weather Trio"},
	{"question": "Uxie, Mesprit, and Azelf are known as...?", "answer": "The Lake guardians"},
	{"question": "Dialga, Palkia, and Giratina are known as...?", "answer": "The Legendary dragons"},
	{"question": "Cresselia, and Darkrai are known as...?", "answer": "The Lunar duo"},
	{"question": "Phione, and Manaphy are known as...?", "answer": "The Sea guardians"}
]}
